https://www.roxleymodels.co.uk/conditions.php?osCsid=i87mrm6j35fgcjj68rok7ai5q2

0 items
A.B.GEEAirfixBachman ScenecraftBachmann BranchlineBachmann Narrow GaugeBachmann ScenecraftCarreraCitadelCorgiCorgi - Original OmnibusCorgi ClassicsDCC ConceptsDeluxe MaterialsDolu - Toy FactoryFallerFleischmannGaugemasterGaugemaster StructuresGilbowGraham FarishGraham Farish ScenecraftHornbyHornby RailroadHumbrolK&M CountrysceneKatoLittle TikesMetcalfeModelmakerOxfordOxford RailPecoPeco ScenePlastic RatioPreiserProsesRevellRocoRoxley ModelsScalextricScentosSkaledaleTamiyaTasma ProductsTobarTooky ToysVigaWills KitsWoodland ScenicsXuron
Home
Catalog
Conditions of Use
Conditions of Use
In using this website you are deemed to have read and agreed to the following terms and conditions:
Returns Policy Summary
You can choose within 14 days of receipt to return items you have bought, without needing an excuse, for a full refund as long as they are unused and the retail packaging is undamaged - so that the item is resellable as new. You pay the return postage. Please make sure to package the item properly so that it arrives undamaged and without stickers on the retail box. Please contact us first so that we know it's coming.
If you believe the goods are faulty please contact us first so that we can trouble-shoot before returning and to organise the postage.
Privacy Statement
We are committed to protecting your privacy. Authorized employees within the company on a need to know basis only use any information collected from individual customers. We constantly review our systems and data to ensure the best possible service to our customers. Parliament has created specific offences for unauthorised actions against computer systems and data. We will investigate any such actions with a view to prosecuting and/or taking civil proceedings to recover damages against those responsible
Confidentiality
We are registered under the Data Protection Act 1998 and as such, any information concerning the Client and their respective Client Records may be passed to third parties. However, Client records are regarded as confidential and therefore will not be divulged to any third party, other than our manufacturers/suppliers and, if legally required to do so, to the appropriate authorities. Customers have the right to request sight of, and copies of any and all Customer Records we keep, on the proviso that we are given reasonable notice of such a request. Customers are requested to retain copies of any literature issued in relation to the provision of our services. Where appropriate, we shall issue Customers with appropriate written information, handouts or copies of records as part of an agreed contract, for the benefit of both parties.
We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party except as required to deliver your order, nor will we use your e-mail address for unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by this Company will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products.
Disclaimer
Exclusions and Limitations
The information on this web site is provided on an "as is" basis. To the fullest extent permitted by law, this Company:
§ excludes all representations and warranties relating to this website and its contents or which is or may be provided by any affiliates or any other third party, including in relation to any inaccuracies or omissions in this website and/or the Company’s literature; and
§ excludes all liability for damages arising out of or in connection with your use of this website. This includes, without limitation, direct loss, loss of business or profits (whether or not the loss of such profits was foreseeable, arose in the normal course of things or you have advised this Company of the possibility of such potential loss), damage caused to your computer, computer software, systems and programs and the data thereon or any other direct or indirect, consequential and incidental damages.
This Company does not, however, exclude liability for death or personal injury caused by its negligence. The above exclusions and limitations apply only to the extent permitted by law. None of your statutory rights as a consumer are affected.
Payment
Cash or Personal Cheque, all major Credit/Debit Cards, Bankers Draft or BACS Transfer are all acceptable methods of payment. Our Terms are payment in full within thirty days. All goods remain the property of the Company until paid for in full and will not be sent out until payment has cleared.
Returned cheques will incur a £25 charge to cover banking fees and administrative costs.
Cancellation Policy
Minimum 24 hours notice of cancellation required. Notification for instance, in person, via email, mobile phone ‘text message’, or any other means will be accepted subject to confirmation in writing. We reserve the right to levy a £30 charge to cover any subsequent administrative expenses.
Refunds Policy
Both the Customer and we have the right to terminate any Services Agreement for any reason, including the ending of services that are already underway. No refunds shall be offered, where a Service is deemed to have begun and is, for all intents and purposes, underway. Any monies that have been paid to us which constitute payment in respect of the provision of unused Services, shall be refunded.
Availability
Unless otherwise stated, the services featured on this website are only available within the United Kingdom, or in relation to postings from the United Kingdom. All advertising is intended solely for the United Kingdom market. You are solely responsible for evaluating the fitness for a particular purpose of any downloads, programs and text available through this site. Redistribution or republication of any part of this site or its content is prohibited, including such by framing or other similar or any other means, without the express written consent of the Company. The Company does not warrant that the service from this site will be uninterrupted, timely or error free, although it is provided to the best ability. By using this service you thereby indemnify this Company, its employees, agents and affiliates against any loss or damage, in whatever manner, howsoever caused.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Additionally, for systems administration, detecting usage patterns and troubleshooting purposes, our web servers automatically log standard access information including browser type, access times/open mail, URL requested, and referral URL. This information is not shared with third parties and is used only within this Company on a need-to-know basis. Any individually identifiable information related to this data will never be used in any way different to that stated above without your explicit permission.
Links to this website
You may not create a link to any page of this website without our prior written consent. If you do create a link to a page of this website you do so at your own risk and the exclusions and limitations set out above will apply to your use of this website by linking to it.
Links from this website
We do not monitor or review the content of other parties’ websites which are linked to from this website. Opinions expressed, or material appearing on such websites, are not necessarily shared or endorsed by us and should not be regarded as the publisher of such opinions or material. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices, or content, of these sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site & to read the privacy statements of these sites. You should evaluate the security and trustworthiness of any other site connected to this site or accessed through this site yourself, before disclosing any personal information to them. This Company will not accept any responsibility for any loss or damage in whatever manner, howsoever caused, resulting from your disclosure to third parties of personal information.
Copyright Notice
Copyright and other relevant intellectual property rights exists on all text relating to the Company’s services and the full content of this website.
Communication
We have several different e-mail addresses for different queries. These, & other contact information, can be found on our Contact Us link on our website or via Company literature or via the Company’s stated telephone No.
General
The laws of England and Wales govern these terms and conditions. By accessing this website and buying our products you consent to these terms and conditions and to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English courts in all disputes arising out of such access. If any of these terms are deemed invalid or unenforceable for any reason (including, but not limited to the exclusions and limitations set out above), then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be severed from these terms and the remaining terms will continue to apply. Failure of the Company to enforce any of the provisions set out in these Terms and Conditions and any Agreement, or failure to exercise any option to terminate, shall not be construed as waiver of such provisions and shall not affect the validity of these Terms and Conditions or of any Agreement or any part thereof, or the right thereafter to enforce each and every provision. These Terms and Conditions shall not be amended, modified, varied or supplemented except in writing and signed by duly authorised representatives of the Company.
Notification of Changes
The Company reserves the right to change these conditions from time to time as it sees fit and your continued use of the site will signify your acceptance of any adjustment to these terms. If there are any changes to our privacy policy, we will announce that these changes have been made on our home page and on other key pages on our site. If there are any changes in how we use our site customers’ Personally Identifiable Information, notification by e-mail or postal mail will be made to those affected by this change. Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on our web site 30 days prior to these changes taking place. You are therefore advised to re-read this statement on a regular basis
Continue
Categories
2019 Releases2020 Hornby Centenary YearRailwayScalextricAirfixTamiya KitsCarrera Slot CarsPaints & GluesDiecastRoxleysVehicle KitsMini ModellerRemote ControlBooks & PostcardsCataloguesGlidersK&S MetalsTakom KitsDiscounts
We Accept
Specials
Hornby - R3552 GWR 4-6-0 Grange Class 'Aberporth Grange' 6860£132.25£119.02
Bestsellers
Hornby - R8262 - 4th Radius Curve 45 deg (OO/HO)PECO - ST-11 - Double Straight (N)Hornby - R610 - Short Straight (OO/HO)PECO - SL-310 - Metal Conductiing Rail Joiners (N/OO-9)PECO - SL-E91 Small Radius Right Hand (Electrofrog) - Code 100ST-200 Standard StraightPlastic Sheet A4 White 0.75mmPECO - ST-201 - Double Straight, Code 100 (00 Gauge)PECO - SL-110 - Fine Standard Rail Joiners Code 75 (HO/OO)Hornby - R8103 TTS Sound Decoder - Class 47
